necel.com 2010-12-30

# Privacy Policy | Renesas Electronics

## Privacy Policy

This site is maintained by Renesas Electronics Corporation ("Renesas"). Protecting your privacy is important to Renesas. By ensuring that you are aware of and understand this Online Privacy Statement, we can provide you with better service. Please take a moment to read the following statement to learn how we handle your personally identifiable information.  
By using this web site, you agree to the terms of this Online Privacy Statement and to our collection and use of information for the purposes stated below.

  1. Scope of Application  
This Online Privacy Statement applies only to the collection and use of information collected online on this site (http://www.renesas.com). Other web sites that may be affiliated with Renesas may have different privacy statements.
  2. Information  
We may collect your personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") when you use our web site. This information may include your name, mailing address, phone number, and e-mail address. When ordering a product or requesting service information, participating in certain promotional activities, completing surveys, and corresponding with us, we may ask for certain Personal Information. Personal Information is not collected on this web site unless you choose to provide it to us. If you are on a part of our web site that requires you to provide your Personal Information, it will be clear what Personal Information we are requesting.  
We may also collect information that is provided to us by your browser. This may include information on the browser you used to come to our web site, the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the web site that you visited just before visiting our web site, which pages on our web site you visit, any search terms you entered, which URL you go to next, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address.
  3. Use of your Information  
Information is collected and used in various ways, including those below. 
    1. Browsing  
When you visit our site or click on advertisements or promotional areas on the site. This information is collected to help run our site more efficiently, to gather broad demographic information, to monitor the level of activity on our site, and to evaluate the effectiveness of advertising and promotion.
    2. Technical Support  
When you request technical support for your Renesas products. This information is necessary to identify your products or systems, understand the configuration of the products, diagnose your questions, and provide solutions.
    3. Online Surveys and Polling  
When you volunteer to complete surveys or participate in polls. We use this information to improve our products and services.
    4. Promotional Activities  
When you enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask you for information such as your name, address and e-mail address to administer the program or activity, to send you promotional e-mails, notify winners and make the winners' list publicly available in compliance with laws which may apply to such activities.
    5. Newsletters and Promotional E-mails  
As a service to our customers, we may e-mail to you newsletters, promotional information and other information, using your Personal Information collected online. These e-mails will only be sent to you if you have agreed to receive them or if you have the right to opt out from further receiving them.
    6. Contact Information  
If you contact us, we may keep a record of your correspondence or comments, including any information therein. We use this information to help us provide better service.
  4. Sharing your Personal Information  
Unless we have your permission, we will share the Personal Information you provide online only with other Renesas entities or with entities that provide services to Renesas or are business partners of Renesas, and only for legitimate purposes including those described herein. Personal Information we collect online is used for responding to inquiries, processing orders, keeping you informed about your order status, for statistical purposes, for improving our site and its performance, for developing better products and services, to serve advertisements, contests, surveys and promotions, and to notify you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you.  
Renesas (or part of it) or its related entitles could merge with or be acquired by another business entity or their respective assets could be acquired. Should such a combination or acquisition occur, you should expect that Renesas would share some or all of your Personal Information to continue serving you and other users of our web site.  
Occasionally, we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide your Personal Information to the appropriate authorities. We will disclose your Personal Information if required by law, upon receipt of a court order or subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement authorities any activities that we, in good faith, believe to be unlawful.
  5. Use of Cookies and Web Beacons  
A "cookie" is a small data file that a web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. We use cookies to better serve you when you return to our site. Some of our web pages may send cookies when you visit our site, make purchases, respond to online surveys or promotions, participate in a contest, or request information. Accepting the cookies used on our site enables our web server to identify your system by reading the cookie that has been stored on your system, but our web server cannot identify you unless you enter your Personal Information. Cookies that are placed when visiting our site cannot be used to obtain your Personal Information at another site.  
The information collected online permits us to analyze traffic patterns on our site. This can enable us over time to provide users with a better experience on our site by improving the content and making it easier to use.  
Depending on the browser used, you can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it, and you can also set your browser to turn off cookies. However, if you do so, some areas of this site may not function properly, or you will be required to re-enter your Personal Information to use an area of this site.  
We may also use web beacon technologies to better tailor the site to provide better customer service. A web beacon is a single pixel GIF that allows a web site to count users who have visited that page or access certain cookies. These web beacons may be placed on specific pages across this web site. When a visitor accesses these pages, an anonymous notice of that visit is generated which may be processed by us or by our vendors. These web beacons work in conjunction with cookies. If you don't want to associate your anonymous cookie information with your visits to these pages, depending on the browser used, you can set your browser to turn off cookies.
  6. Children's Privacy  
If you are under the age of 16, please make sure that you provide Personal Information only after obtaining your parental consent.
  7. Protecting your Personal Information  
While Renesas does not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur, Renesas does take care in maintaining the security of your Personal Information and in preventing unauthorized access to it.
  8. Links to other Web Sites  
Parts of our site contain links to our subsidiaries and third-party web sites for your convenience and information. If you use these links, you will leave Renesas's web site. When you access these other sites, even ones that may contain the Renesas mark, please understand that we do not control the content and are not responsible for the privacy practices of that web site. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each web site you visit. This Online Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those web sites linked to our site. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit Personal Information.
  9. Changes to this Statement  
Renesas reserve the right to change this Online Privacy Statement at any time. Any such changes will be posted in this Privacy Statement.
  10. Applicable Laws  
Renesas will protect your Personal Information in accordance with the laws of Japan.
  11. Contact Us  
Please contact the Webmaster through the "Contact Us (Others)" section if you have any questions or comments about the above.
